QUENTIN DAVIS

C++ | C# GAME PROGRAMMER



ADDRESS 1607 Gary Avenue, Pensacola, 32505, United States



PHONE NUMBER (850) 977-1695



EMAIL davisq1991@yahoo.com

I am a programmer with 3 years of experience and continuously growing! I have a game design mindset and a passion for creating and playing games. I possess a great understanding of object-oriented programming. I am eager to collaborate with a studio, where I can showcase my excellent communication, technical and problem-solving skills. As I am sure my experience in prototyping, debugging, iterative design, attention to detail, and dedication can help elevate any project! As a designer and programmer by heart, I intuitively know how to improve on weaker aspects of game design while reviewing and playing games.

WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS

LinkedIn: Quentin Davis | LinkedIn

GitHub: Code Example

EDUCATION

Bachelors Degree in Computer Science

University of Phoenix

Currently pursuing

Associates in Computer Science Pensacola State College

Transferred

SKILLS

• SQL (Programming Language)

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

Al for Better Lives/Remote/Jan 2020-Present

- Design and implement efficient low-level systems to support higher-level pipelines
- Debug and maintain responsibility for written code
- Collaborate with senior programmers to ensure all project deadlines are met
- Interact and communicate effectively with management, while independently working on assigned tasks with limited supervision
- •Worked on a WinForms knowledge representation toll which enables end users to store real world knowledge In a database used for AI applications

UNREAL C++ DEVELOPER

Independent Project/Remote/Mar 2018-Present

- Develop state-of-the-art AI technology to create AI behaviours and abilities
- Implement cutting-edge menus with grid-based inventory in C++, allowing users to decide which items to equip inside the widget
- Resolve challenging and complex problems around the Unreal engine to create a seamless user experience

MEMBER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

 HyperText Markup Language (HTML) 	 Analysed, researched, and resolved problems and discrepancies related to member's accounts/loans
• Adobe Photoshop	• Communicated effectively with internal team members as well as external parties, including members and their close families
Unreal Engine	• Regularly communicates and coordinates with financial institutions to obtain member information. (Payoffs, interest rates, payment, etc.)
• C++	 Counsels members regarding appropriate loan options, and loan status and maintains confidentiality of members' information.
• C#	GAME ADVISOR & SALES REPRESENTATIVE GameStop/Pensacola/Nov 2015-Jan 2017
Game Development	Greeted incoming customers
Visual Studio	Provided customers with technical support in person and via telephone
Object-Oriented Programming	Operated cash register, including scanning merchandise and cash tendering
Documented Design	Oversaw store inventory levels and restock as needed
Visual Code	 Collected and entered customer information for reservations, trade-ins, returns, defective merchandise, subscription, and memberships
• GitHub	 Increased customer confidence and loyalty by providing courteous and prompt responses
Gameplay Programming	 Resolved customer complaints and/or appropriately escalate customer concerns to management when needed
• Visual Basic	 Educated customers on different promotions or specials and suggested products when appropriate
Games Testing	 Monitored surroundings for theft or any action that is illegal and or against company policy than need to be reported to management
 Communication (verbal and written) 	Floated to different locations for support staffing needs
• Teamwork	
Clip Studio Paint	
Microsoft Office	

Navy Federal Credit Union/Pensacola/Mar 2018-Sep 2019